Guide to the Committee of 100 on the Federal City records [Part I], 1932-2003 MS2017
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Financial records, 1966-1999; Circa 1970 - Circa 1999; MS2017 Series 5
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Bank Statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets., 1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Bank statements, Cancelled Checks and Deposit Tickets, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Bills and Balance Sheets, 1971-1974 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Checkbook and Stubs, 1970-1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Checkbook and Stubs, 1974-1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence on Contributions to Legal Funds, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence on Contributions to Legal Funds, 1972-1978 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence on Legal Fund, 1966-1970 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence on PIPA Account, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1966-1976 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1977-1982 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Financial Notes, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - IRS Tax Forms, 1966-1979 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Mimeograph Bills and Receipts, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Mimeograph Bills and Receipts, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Mimeograph Bills and Receipts, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Mimeograph Bills and Receipts, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Mimeograph Bills and Receipts, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Mimeograph Bills and Receipts, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Mimeograph Bills and Receipts, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Mimeograph Bills and Receipts, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Non Profit Forms and Applications, 1966-1973 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Receipt and Disbursment Notebook, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1975-1982 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Committee of 100 - bank statements, receipts, bills paid - miscellaneous, 1989; Series 5 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Bank statements: Calvert, 1987; Series 5 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Committee of 100 - Invoices, receipts, etc., 1988; Series 5 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Committee of 100 bank statements and first variable accounts, 1988; Series 5 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Committee of 100 - bills paid (1 of 2), 1988; Series 5 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Committee of 100 - bills paid (2 of 2), 1988; Series 5 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Johnston-Lemon & Co., Inc., 1982; Series 5 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Invoices, receipts, correspondence, misc., 1994; Series 5 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Luncheons: Cosmos - J.L. Miller, 1992-1993; Series 5 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Current Cosmos lunch dues and paid membership, 1993; Series 5 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Crestar Statements, circa 1966 – circa 1995; Series 5 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Financial records: deposits, receipts, checks, circa 1966– circa 1995; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Financial records: correspondence, expense reports, published materials, circa 1980 - circa 1989; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Bills (Cosmos Club, A-I-A, Trustee Luncheon, 1985; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Printing, 1984; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Bills and receipts - paid, 1985; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees: Financial records, correspondence, issues, 1980s; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - C100: Meeting Locations, 1987-1996; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - The National Capital Planning Commissions Monumental Core Plan, 1996; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - C100 History 2, 1995; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Secretarial 1983 Bills, 1983-1983; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Bills, receipts, financial reports, 1984; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Return of Organization Exempt from Income Tax Forms, 1989-1994; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - C100 Tax Returns [1 of 3], circa 1970 - circa 1999; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - C100 Tax Returns [2 of 3], circa 1970 - circa 1999; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - C100 Tax Returns [3 of 3], circa 1970 - circa 1999; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Committee of 100, 1986; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Committee of 100 bills paid, 1985; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Committee of 100 bills paid, 1986; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Ledger, 1972-1982; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Board of Trustees: member lists, 1992-1996; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Statement from Dorn McGrath on Proposed Stadium, 1993; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Crestar Statements - C100, 1994; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Crestar Statements - PIPA, 1994; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Committee of 100 Organization Files, 1992; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Committee of 100 Invoies, receipts, deposits, correspondence, misc., 1993; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Committee of 100 receipts, bank statements, checks, and miscellaneous bills paid, 1990; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Committee of 100 receipts, bank statements, checks, and miscellaneous bills paid, 1991; Series 5 (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - Crestar Statements, 1992-1993; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Tax documents, bills, 1994-1995; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Crestar Statements, 1989-1989; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Crestar Statements, 1991; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - City Duplicating Word Pro, 1987; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Membership lunches, trustee lunches, 1987; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Harrison Institute, 1987; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - NS&T State and Department, 1986; Series 5 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Subject/Issues files, 1954-1998; MS2017 Series 6
  This series contains correspondence, reports, publications, pamphlets, memorandum, Congressional bills, newspaper articles, maps and blueprints. This material dates form 1954-91. The broad subjects within the collection include city planning, ecology/conservation, historic preservation, and transportation both general, and highways. These materials represent the real involvement of the Committee with the various planning aspects of the Nation's Capital. They contain information on citizens groups, court cases, and planning commissions which shows how the Committee of 100 used its influence to solve many of the problems facing the District of Columbia.
  The material related to transportation contains important information on the Three Sisters Bridge controversy, the Volpe Trial, and Interstate construction in the D.C. Metropolitan Area. For the topic of city planning there is extensive documentation on the Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation and the National Capital Planning Commission and blueprints of projects such as the Old Post Office and Federal Triangle.
  - National Capital Planning Commission (NCPC): "City Planning and Zoning Regulations,", 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - NCPC: Comprehensive Plan, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - NCPC: Comprehensive Planning Maps, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - NCPC: Congressional Bill HR 12708, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - NCPC: Convention/Sports Arena Complex, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - NCPC: Developmental Plan, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - NCPC: Downtown Design and Development, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - NCPC: Downtown Heliport Study, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - NCPC: Federal Capital Improvements Program, 1982-1986 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - NCPC: Federal Goals for the National Capital, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - NCPC: Friendship Heights Uptown Center, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - NCPC: Reorganization of NCPC, correspondence, 1973-1982 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - NCPC: Resolutions and Correspondence, 1960-1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - NCPC: Transportation Planning Acts, 1968-1979 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - NCPC: Transportation Plans, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - NCPC: Urban Design, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - NCPC: Urban Design Study of Constitution and Independence Ave., 1980 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - NCPC: The Urban River, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - NCPC: Zoning Correspondence, 1977-1981 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - NCPC: Zoning Correspondence, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    General note
    Selected items from this folder are listed below. Please note that this is not a comprehensive list of materials within this folder.
    - General Services Administration, Federal Triangle--Master Plan, Executive Director's Summary of Issues and Options, 1982 April 30; Item 1
    - General Services Administration, Federal Triangle--Master Plan, Report to the General Services Administration (Draft), 1982 April 30; Item 2
    - Federal Triangle Master Plan, Report of the Joint Committee on Landmarks, 1982 April 21; Item 3
  - NCPC: Zoning and Lawsuits, miscellaneous material, 1966-1971 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - PADC: Annual Report, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - PADC: Annual Report, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - PADC: Background Information, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Selected items from this folder are described below. Please note that this is not a comprehensive list of materials within this folder.
    - Statement by Louis Justement for the Committee of 100, 1965 March 05; Item 1
  - PADC: Copies of Congressional Bills, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - PADC: Federal Triangle Correspondence, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - PADC: Federal Triangle Master Plan, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - PADC: General Correspondence, 1972-1982 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - PADC: Hearings, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Statement of Karen Gordon Don't Tear It Down Before the Subcommittee on Governmental Operations and Metropolitan Affairs of the Committee on the District of Columbia, 1981 October 14; Item 1
    - Statement of Max N. Berry, Chairman Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation, Appearing before Subcommittee on Government Operations and Metropolitan Affairs House Committee on the District of Columbia, undated; Item 2
  - PADC: Historic Preservation of Buildings, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Preservation of Historic Buildings in the Pennsylvania Avenue National Historic Site, undated; Item 1
    - Preservation and Enhancement of Historic Values in the Uncommitted Development Areas of the Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation, undated; Item 2
  - PADC: Housing Guidelines, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Testimony of the Metropolitan Washington Planning and Housing Association Presented to the Subcommittee on Public Lands and Nation [sic] Parks of the Interior Committee U.S. House of Representatives, 1982 March 02; Item 1
  - PADC: Housing in Eastern Sector, correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - PADC: Housing in Eastern Sector, Report, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Selected items from this folder are described below. Please note that this is not a comprehensive list of the materials within this folder.
    - Testimony of the Metropolitan Washington Planning & Housing Association on the Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation presented to the Subcommittee on Public Lands and National Parks of the Committee of the Interior and Insular Affairs U.S. House of Representatives, 1982 April 22; Item 1
    - Statement of Karen Gorden on Behalf of Don't Tear It Down, 1982 April 23; Item 2
  - PADC: John Marshall Place Park, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - PADC: Navy Memorial Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - PADC: Navy Memorial Development Reports, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - PADC: Miscellaneous News Clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - PADC: Organizational Information, 1975-1982 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - PADC: Pennsylvania Avenue Development Briefings, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - PADC: Pennsylvania Avenue Plan, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - PADC: Miscellaneous Material, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Zoning: Building Height Act, 1910 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Zoning: Building Heights, correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Zoning: Building Heights, reports, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Zoning: "Bus Shelter Act of 1979 and Mass Transit Advertising Act of 1980,", 1976-1980 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Zoning: Cleveland Park/Connecticut Avenue Downzoning, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Zoning: Cleveland Park/Wisconsin Avenue Rezoning, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Convention Center, 1977-1982 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Data Book "Greater Washington Region,", 1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Dupont Circle, 1973-1981 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Missions and Reciprocity Acts, 1977-1982 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - 14th and U Streets, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Fourways Restaurant Site, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Georgetown Heating and Cooling Plant, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Gray Property (Arlington), 1988 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Zoning Case 79 1, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Judiciary Office Building Development Act, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - McClean Gardens, correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - McClean Gardens, Developmental Proposals, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - McClean Gardens, news clippings, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - McClean Gardens, "Traffic Impact Study,", 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - McCLean Gardens, Petitions for Court Review, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Naval Observatory Precinct Hearing, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Parking Facility Act, 1966-1969 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Parking Facilities Report by Congress, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Parking, news clippings, 1966-1972 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Parking Problems, correspondence, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Parking Problems, correspondence, 1967-1982 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Parking Problems, reports, 1966-1969 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Parking Reports, miscellaneous, 1966-1972 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Petitions for Court Review: "44th Street,", 1973 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Petitions for Court Review: "44th Street,", 1974 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Phillips Estate, correspondence, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Phillips Estate, correspondence, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - PUD Regulations, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Reorganization Plan 1967, White House (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Shepherd Park/Gateway Project, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Sidewalk Cafes, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Street and Alley Closings, correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Street and Alley Closings, correspondence, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Street and Alley Closings, correspondence, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Techworld Appeal Case, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Techworld appeal Case, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Techworld Development, Committee Material, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Techworld Hearings with Convention Center Associates, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Techworld Hearings with Convention Center Associates, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Techworld, NCPC materials, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Techworld, news clippings, 1984-1986 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Vice President's Residence, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Wisconsin Avenue Downzoning, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Whitehaven Woods Development Plans, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Zoning Regulations of D.C., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Regulations Amendment Act of 1986 (Mini Jails) (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Other Materials, 1961-1971 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Other Materials, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Other Materials, 1973-1976 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Other Materials, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Other Materials, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Other Materials, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Other Materials, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Other Materials, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Court Cases and Appeals, 1968-1977 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous News Clippings, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - APCA Directory of Planning Agencies, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - APCA Planning and Civic Comment Pamphlets, 1940-1965 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - APCA "Rush Hour Commuting from Virginia to Washington,", 1964 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - APCA Trustees Minutes, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Appropriations, "Proposed 1967 FY Budget for D.C.,", 1966 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Civic Groups, reports, 1964-1975 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - COG Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - COG and PAC's, 1979-1981 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Comprehensive Plan 1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Downtown Afoot: Pedestrian Report, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Downtown Progress "F Street Plaza Proposal,", 1971 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Downtown Progress Newsletters, 1962-1966 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Federal Capital Improvement Program for the National Capital Region, 1979-1984 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Greater Washington Research Center, "Condition Report,", 1980 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - High Technology Industry in D.C., 1984 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Housing and Economic Development Bill, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - James Madison Annex to Library of Congress, 1962-1971 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Land Use Directory, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Mayoral Campaign on Land Use, 1976-1982 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Mayoral Candidates, "Question Log,", 1982 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Mayoral Comprehensive Plan, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Memorials and Monuments, correspondence, 1961-1982 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Memorials and Monuments, "Ellipse Police Memorial,", 1987 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Metropolitan Policy Guide Summary Report, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Nelson Commission Reviews, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Planning an Housing Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Rock Creek and Other Parks (Booklet), 1967 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Urban America "City Magazine," November, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Capitol Master Plan, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Washington Buildings Congress Bulletin, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies "D.C. Reorganization,", 1967 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Air Pollution, "GWCCA Minutes and Memberhsip Info.,", 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Air Pollution, miscellaneous correspondence, 1967-1973 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Air Pollution, "MWCCA Air Pollution Studies,", 1970-1972 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Air Pollution, news clippings, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Air Pollution, Publications and Environmental Reports, 1966-1973 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Air Pollution, Statements by Comm. of 100, 1967-1972 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Bald Eagle Refuge, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Blue Plains Wastewater Treatment Plant, "Sludge Management Study,", 1989 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Conservation Foundation Reports and Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Conservation, General Correspondence, 1966-1980 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Conservation, miscellaneous news clippings, 1966-1971 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Environmental Policy Bibliographies, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Environmental Proposals, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Ecology/Conservation: "Federal Triangle Environmental Impact Statement,", 1982 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Ecology/Conservation: The Greathouse Tract (Potomac Palisades), miscellaneous material, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Greathouse Tract (Potomac Palisades), Zoning Application Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Glover Archbold Park, correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Glover Archbold Park, "Development Civil Case,", 1986 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Mason Neck Park, correspondence, 1966-1982 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Mason Neck Park, Funding Information, 1966-1982 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Mason Neck Park, news clippings, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Northern Virginia Conservation Council Materials, 1971-1978 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Ecology/Conservation: "Open Space in D.C.," correspondence, 1962-1972 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Park Conservation, miscellaneous correspondence, 1960-1968 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Pesticides, "Correspondence on DDT,", 1966-1967 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Pesticides, "Report on Crop Dusting,", 1970 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Port America "Environmental Concerns,", 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Ecology/Conservation: "Potomac Basin Center" Newsletters, 1968-1970 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Potomac River Basin, Commission Newsletters, 1966-1972 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Potomac River Basin, Committee Reports, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Potomac River Basin, General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Potomac River Basin, reports, 1966-1969 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Potomac Interim Report to the President, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Potomac Valley Conservation and Recreation Council Newsletters, 1966-1972 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Potomac Valley Conservation and Recreation Council Newsletters, 1970-1972 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Potomac Weir, correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Trees, correspondence, 1972-1981 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Trees, news clippings, 1972-1981 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Trees, reports, 1964-1972 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Water, Correspondence on Water Supply, 1973-1980 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Water, Correspondence on Water Treatment, 1972-1981 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Water, "Metropolitan Washington Water Quality Management Plan,", 1978 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Water, News Clippings an Water Pollution, 1972-1982 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Water, "Report on Alternative Water Supply Programs in D.C.,", 1974 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Water, "Report on Sixes Bridge/Verona Dam,", 1973 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Water, "Reports and Pamphlets on Water Conservation,", 1974-1979 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Ecology/Conservation: Wilderness Society Newsletters, 1967-1970 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Historic Preservation: Articles and Press Releases on General Preservation, 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Selected items from this folder are described below. Please note that this is not a complete list of materials within this folder.
    - Don't Tear It Down: Current and Continuing Activities, 1980 May; Item 1
  - Historic Preservation: Babcock Macomb/PIPA Project, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Historic Preservation: Bill 194 "Tax on Historic Buildings," correspondence, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Historic Preservation: Cathedral Mansions Apartment Complex, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Historic Preservation: City Post Office, "Historic Structure Report,", 1987 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Historic Preservation: City Post Office, Interviews, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Historic Preservation: City Post Office, NCPC Agendas and Correspondence, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Historic Preservation: City Post Office, NCPC Report, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Historic Preservation: City Post Office, news clippings, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Historic Preservation: City Post Office, Report by Historic Preservation Review Board, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Historic Preservation: City Post Office, miscellaneous reports, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 11)